http://www.americanpress.com/site/privacy.html

What's Open
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:• To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)• To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)• To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature• To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Do we use cookies?Yes.Third party vendorsIncluding Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings or opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.www.americanpress.com4900 Highway 90East Lake Charles,Louisiana 70615United States of Americanwebmaster@americanpress.comPhone: 337-433-3000
Mozaic SocialDiscover Southwest Louisiana businesses on social media
Local
Quarantine guidelines relaxed for schools
The Louisiana Department of Health adopted updated quarantine guidance from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Monday that will… Read more
Future of Beauregard health unit in question
A dismal voter turnout on Saturday may have resulted in the loss of programs and operations in the future at the Beauregard Parish health unit.
Read more
Tourism advocates: Supporting area’s treasures will help speed recovery
Visit Lake Charles — Southwest Louisiana’s and Lake Charles’ tourism advocate — has faced unique challenges this year between COVID-19 and Hur… Read more
State
Winning numbers drawn in 'Pick 4' game
Facebook
Twitter
WhatsApp
SMS
Email
BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — The winning number… Read more
Disney unveils plans to stream a galaxy of new series, films
US set to execute 1st of 5 inmates before Biden inauguration
World carbon dioxide emissions drop 7% in pandemic-hit 2020
Exposure feared after New Hampshire speaker dies of COVID-19
© Copyright 2020 American Press, 4900 Highway 90 East Lake Charles, LA | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
